### **Kevin Gorski**

804 Summer Hawk Drive #1202 Longmont, CO 80504

T (720) 339-0925 kevin.gorski@gmail.com

kevingorski.com

### **PROFILE**

I am a software architect and developer that turns good ideas into great products for start-ups and small businesses. In seven years of professional software development, I've worked with companies from early stage start-ups to those with hundreds of thousands of customers to build software that improves their existing businesses or creates new ones and I'm looking for a new opportunity to build something great.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**SOFTWARE ARCHITECT, AMADEUS CONSULTING — MAY 2008 - NOVEMBER 2010**Amadeus Consulting is a custom software development company and my experiences there were across many different projects and technologies. As an architect, I was also working at a higher level to ensure the success of projects and the teams that worked on them:

- · Created high-level system designs with specific details around budget, risk mitigation, and flexibility
- Introduced or strengthened quality-improving practices like iterative design and development, continuous integration, and layered application patterns
- Trained and educated other developers through code and design reviews, mentoring, and introductory presentations on development topics like jQuery and Dependency Injection
- Created and improved a standardized build & continuous integration process
- · Evaluated new tools and processes to integrate into everyday development

An example of a project I worked on as an architect was an enterprise system for an equipment rental startup. I evaluated the high-level and detailed business requirements for technical feasibility and created the development plan that identified potential risks, provided a plan to mitigate them, and showed how we could use continuous integration to show our value and progress to the client throughout the project. In addition to being the primary developer for most of the project, I was the technical lead for the team that did form. I led design discussions, clarified requirements, and worked with the team lead to ensure that the development team was given well-defined tasks that made sense in the context of the larger project and that we could provide the best solution possible.

### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, AMADEUS CONSULTING — JUNE 2004 - MAY 2008

- · Worked independently and as part of a team
- · Quickly learned new systems and technologies
- Evaluated the feasibility and impact of proposed features
- · Balanced value delivered with budget available

An example of a project I worked on here was an eCommerce SaaS Startup that hosted branded online stores for its customers, who then sold merchandise to the end customer. I started on this project as part of a small team, but over time became the sole developer and eventually trained others to work with the system. During the course of the project I was in constant communication with both technical and non-technical stakeholders in the

project to better understand their requirements and support requests. Some of the features implemented included:

- · Multiple payment processors
- · Third party system integration / single sign on
- · Flexible reporting
- · Inventory managment
- · Coupon and discount system

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN, ROSE-HULMAN VENTURES — JUNE 2003 - AUGUST 2003

Enhanced a computer vision-based 3D scanning application's efficiency and accuracy with creative hardware additions and updates to its C code base.

## **EDUCATION**

Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology — BS, Computer Science, 2004

### **SKILLS**

C#, ASP.NET WebForms, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, Objective-C, T-SQL, LINQ to SQL, NHibernate & Fluent NHibernate, Autofac, WCF, Software Architecture and design principles, Subversion, Git, Node.js

### **REFERRALS**

Recommendations for my past work can be viewed on my LinkedIn profile (http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=5063117#recommendations) and referral information is available on request.